This is one small step for woman, one giant leap for woman-kind
ariana grande: excuse me, i love you is a music,
documentary film directed by Paul Dugdale.
Ariana Grande takes the stage in London for her Sweetener World Tour and shares a
behind-the-scenes look at her life in rehearsal and on the road.
Self, played by Ariana Grande.
Self - Creative Director / Dancer, played by Scott Nicholson.
Self - Creative Director / Dancer, played by Brian Nicholson.
Self - Dance Captain, played by Joesar Alva.
Self - Dance Captain, played by Cory Graves.
Self - Dancer, played by Bong Buño.
Ariana Grande: Excuse Me, I Love You (stylized in all lowercase) is a 2020 American concert film that
follows Ariana Grande on-stage and behind the scenes of the Sweetener World Tour in 2019.
The film was released on December 21, 2020, on Netflix, in
commemoration of the first anniversary of the tour's conclusion.
The release of the film was preceded by the live album K Bye for Now (SWT Live) (2019),
which was released a year prior and features audio recordings from said tour.